





## **Notable Achievements**

LBS Game Awards

My games were nominated for the LBS Game Awards 2017, 2018, and 2019, a nation-wide competition between gymnasium schools in Sweden

Best of r/WritingPrompts 2019 Awarded for my short story "Picture of a Thousand Words" in the Reality Fiction category.

## **Professional Skillset**

I'm a motivated and joyful tools/engine programmer, with a drive to finish what I start. My active interest in games development stems from a combination of my creative, yet critical thinking as well as from my headstrong passion for my projects and the challenges they present. Although I primarily focus on programming in C# and Unity, I have experience working in both C++ and Java. Throughout my years of study, I have developed my leadership and teamworking skills to the point where I actively lead the team when the situation requires it. I also have an understanding of asset creation and asset optimization.

## Education

University of Portsmouth Computer Games Technology BSc (Hons) 2019 - 2023 (Currently in 1st Year)

Focused primarily on programming, with a generalist set of skills including leadership, pre-production planning, 3D asset creation, and game design fundamentals.

#### LBS Lund

Technology Programme (Graduated with the equivalent of ~BCC in A-levels) 2016 - 2019

Studied in the design and product development branch, with a focus on games development. Passed every programming class with the highest possible marks (A). Focused on attention theory for the final year project.

# Experience

Programmer & Team Lead Four Knights Inn (Technical Game Development @ University of Portsmouth 2019-2020)

A party game aimed at children and pre-teens, created by a team of 8 in Unity.

- Focused on guiding the project throughout the development process and to solve issues regarding motivation and time constraint when they arose.
- Focused on implementing the core gameplay loop, the minigames that had been designed, as well as importing assets and polishing the game to an acceptable level.

Game Developer Delivery Demolition (September 2019 - Ongoing)

A side-project in Unity I'm working on between projects.

- Single-handedly designed, developed, and marketed the game.

Programmer & Marketer Caribbean Waters (December 2018 - May 2019)

A sandbox party game developed as part of an entrepreneurship

- Diligently implemented most gameplay systems, including the player movement and interaction, shop system, quest system, and the ship systems. This led to a complete vertical slice for a major-scale game in the span of 5 months whilst working on other subjects' schoolwork.
- Took charge of marketing both the game and the company LowResViews on multiple social media platforms. The marketing led to the company leading the entrepreneurship course, UF, to actively notice us.

### Interests

Movies and Cinema Writing Story-Driven Games Esports Planning and Running Events



https://www.naomiwiren.com/

business@naomiwiren.com

# Positions of Responsibility

Substitute Teacher LBS Lund - Game Design and English (August 2019 - September 2019)

- Taught the game design students about how to look for inspiration for their games, as well as thinking about how their games will challenge a player.

# Student Representative (University of Portsmouth 2019 - Ongoing)

- Actively reached out to students regarding improving the course modules and the university in its entirety.
- Brought up issues of importance to the course leader.

# Chairman of the Development Committee (LBS Lund 2018 - 2019)

- Started and single-handedly developed a committee under the student body with the intent of improving the average quality of work of the school. This initiative combined with the Equality and Dignity Committee led to the school being awarded for the best social contribution out of all gymnasium schools in Sweden 2018.

## Class Representative for Graduation

(June 2018 - June 2019)

- Took initiative to handle the graduation hurdles during the final year of gymnasium. This includes graduation hats, flatbed ride, champagne breakfast, plate necklaces and sheet signs.
- Was partially responsible for achieving a deal with a graduation hat company that gave every student a discount.
- Helped the second year students come to a similar deal for graduation hats.

## **Testimonials**

#### André Dilles

## Head Teacher of Programming at LBS Lund

Naomi is an ambitious and driven student that doesn't back down from challenges and keeps pushing her own limits. She's creative and a problem solver and she always seeks new ways to improve herself. She's an excellent programmer as well as a Game Designer, with experience in both C# and C++ she has a mind for what's doable in terms of Game Design.

# References

André Dilles

Head Teacher of Programming at LBS Lund

Magnus Robertsson

Founder and CTO of Planeto AB